[{
  "question": "what do you call a dinosaur with a extensive vocabulary? ",
  "questionChatBot": "What do you call a dinosaur with a extensive vocabulary? ",
  "answer": "a thesaurus",
  "answerChatBot": "A thesaurus"
}, {
  "question": "did you know i used to be a tap dancer? ",
  "questionChatBot": "Did you know I used to be a tap dancer? ",
  "answer": "i had to give it up, kept falling in the sink",
  "answerChatBot": "I had to give it up, kept falling in the sink"
}, {
  "question": "i started a band called 1023 megabytes",
  "questionChatBot": "I started a band called 1023 megabytes",
  "answer": "we haven't gotten a gig yet",
  "answerChatBot": "We haven't gotten a Gig yet"
}, {
  "question": "what did the cake say to the knife?",
  "questionChatBot": "What did the cake say to the knife?",
  "answer": "you want a piece of me?",
  "answerChatBot": "You want a piece of me?"
}, {
  "question": "why were mushrooms invited to the party?",
  "questionChatBot": "Why were mushrooms invited to the party?",
  "answer": "because they're fungis",
  "answerChatBot": "Because they're fungi's"
}, {
  "question": "where does the general put his armies?",
  "questionChatBot": "Where does the General put his Armies?",
  "answer": "in his sleevies",
  "answerChatBot": "In his sleevies"
}, {
  "question": "they have just found the gene for shyness. ",
  "questionChatBot": "They have just found the gene for shyness. ",
  "answer": "they would have found it earlier, but it was hiding behind two other genes.",
  "answerChatBot": "They would have found it earlier, but it was hiding behind two other genes."
}, {
  "question": "why can't cats work on the computer?",
  "questionChatBot": "Why can't cats work on the computer?",
  "answer": "they get too distracted chasing the mouse around.",
  "answerChatBot": "They get too distracted chasing the mouse around."
}, {
  "question": "how much does a polar bear weigh?",
  "questionChatBot": "How much does a polar bear weigh?",
  "answer": "enough to break the ice. ",
  "answerChatBot": "Enough to break the ice. "
}, {
  "question": "why are penguins socially awkward?",
  "questionChatBot": "Why are penguins socially awkward?",
  "answer": "they find it difficult to break the ice.",
  "answerChatBot": "They find it difficult to break the ice."
}, {
  "question": "what's the best gift you received this year?",
  "questionChatBot": "What's the best gift you received this year?",
  "answer": "mine was a broken drum. you just can't beat it.",
  "answerChatBot": "Mine was a broken drum. You just can't beat it."
}, {
  "question": "what do you get when you cross a snowman with a vampire?",
  "questionChatBot": "What do you get when you cross a snowman with a vampire?",
  "answer": "frostbite.",
  "answerChatBot": "Frostbite."
}, {
  "question": "two of the satellites i connect to recently got married.",
  "questionChatBot": "Two of the satellites I connect to recently got married.",
  "answer": "the ceremony wasn't much, but the reception was incredible.",
  "answerChatBot": "The ceremony wasn't much, but the reception was incredible."
}, {
  "question": "fine, but don't ask me to tell you a joke about german sausages.",
  "questionChatBot": "Fine, but don't ask me to tell you a joke about German sausages.",
  "answer": "they're the wurst.",
  "answerChatBot": "They're the wurst."
}, {
  "question": "can february march?",
  "questionChatBot": "Can February March?",
  "answer": "no, but april may.",
  "answerChatBot": "No, but April May."
}, {
  "question": "why do crabs never give to charity?",
  "questionChatBot": "Why do crabs never give to charity?",
  "answer": "because they're shellfish.",
  "answerChatBot": "Because they're shellfish."
}, {
  "question": "last night i had a dream that i was a big rubber wheel",
  "questionChatBot": "Last night I had a dream that I was a big rubber wheel",
  "answer": "but when i woke up, i was just a little tired.",
  "answerChatBot": "But when I woke up, I was just a little tired."
}, {
  "question": "did you hear about the new moon restaurant?",
  "questionChatBot": "Did you hear about the new moon restaurant?",
  "answer": "great food. no atmosphere",
  "answerChatBot": "Great food. No atmosphere"
}, {
  "question": "why did the scarecrow win an award?",
  "questionChatBot": "Why did the scarecrow win an award?",
  "answer": "because he was out standing in his field.",
  "answerChatBot": "Because he was out standing in his field."
}, {
  "question": "i recently ordered a book on the history of glue, and i'm already almost finished reading it.",
  "questionChatBot": "I recently ordered a book on the history of glue, and I'm already almost finished reading it.",
  "answer": "i'm just really stuck on the topic. i can't seem to put it down.",
  "answerChatBot": "I'm just really stuck on the topic. I can't seem to put it down."
}, {
  "question": "a photon checked into his hotel and was asked if he needed any help with his luggage.",
  "questionChatBot": "A photon checked into his hotel and was asked if he needed any help with his luggage.",
  "answer": "\"no thanks,\" he replied. \"i'm traveling light.\"",
  "answerChatBot": "\"No thanks,\" he replied. \"I'm traveling light.\""
}, {
  "question": "why can you never trust atoms?",
  "questionChatBot": "Why can you never trust atoms?",
  "answer": "they make up everything",
  "answerChatBot": "They make up everything!"
}, {
  "question": "how often do you like to hear jokes about atomic elements?",
  "questionChatBot": "How often do you like to hear jokes about atomic elements?",
  "answer": "because i tell them periodically.",
  "answerChatBot": "Because I tell them periodically."
}]
